<Group>
  <ToolOneVersion>8</ToolOneVersion>
  <Groups>
    <Group>
      <Name>General</Name>
      <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
      <Groups>
        <Group>
          <Name>Intro Video</Name>
          <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
          <Assets>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Sequenz Audio+Text</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058055</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>world event 3 intro 01</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>trost</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-09-02 16:06</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>Seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-01-30 17:04</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Möglicherweise haben Sie die aktuellen Bewegungen am Aktienmarkt bereits beobachtet. Das Wichtigste in Kürze: Der Wert von Global Trust-Anteilen ist stark gefallen. Wegen einiger unglücklicher Grenzkonflikte mit der Eden Initiative. </Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Möglicherweise haben Sie die aktuellen Bewegungen am Aktienmarkt bereits beobachtet. Das Wichtigste in Kürze: Der Wert von Global Trust-Anteilen ist stark gefallen. Wegen einiger unglücklicher Grenzkonflikte mit der Eden Initiative. </LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>You may or may not be aware of recent stock market movements. To summarize: Global Trust shares dropped sharply in value. Mainly due to some unfortunate territory disputes with the Eden Initiative.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Vous n’êtes peut-être pas au fait des récentes évolutions de la bourse. Pour résumer : la valeur des actions de Global Trust a beaucoup baissé. Notamment à cause de regrettables querelles territoriales avec Eden Initiative.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Non so se sei al corrente degli ultimi movimenti del mercato. In breve: le azioni della Global Trust sono crollate. Principalmente a causa di sfortunate dispute territoriali con Eden Initiative.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Quizá no conozcas los últimos movimientos de la bolsa: las acciones de Global Trust han caído en picado. La causa principal son desafortunadas disputas territoriales con la Iniciativa Edén. </Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Może nie wiesz, co ostatnio dzieje się na giełdzie. W skrócie: akcje Global Trust uległy gwałtownej przecenie. Głównie przez niefortunne spory terytorialne z Eden Initiative.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Akcie Global Trust kvůli šarvátkám s Iniciativou Eden významně poklesly.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Я не знаю, насколько вы в курсе последних событий на фондовой бирже. Вкратце: акции Глобал Траст сильно упали в цене. В основном - из-за этих территориальных споров с Эдем Инишиэйтив.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Möglicherweise haben Sie die aktuellen Bewegungen am Aktienmarkt bereits beobachtet. Um das Wichtigste zusammen zu fassen: Der Wert von Global Trust-Anteilen ist stark gefallen. Auslöser waren hauptsächlich einige unglückliche Grenzkonflikte mit der Eden Initiative. </LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Sequenz Audio+Text</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058056</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>world event 3 intro 02</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>trost</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-09-02 16:07</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-21 18:13</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Dieser Kurssturz hat einen Abwärtstrend ausgelöst, der mit jeder Minute mehr Kapital vernichtet. Um eine weltweite Rezession zu verhindern, haben der Global Trust-Vorstand und Skylar Banes sofortige Gegenmaßnahmen autorisiert.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Dieser Kurssturz hat einen Abwärtstrend ausgelöst, der mit jeder Minute mehr Kapital vernichtet. Um eine weltweite Rezession zu verhindern, haben der Global Trust Vorstand und Skylar Banes sofortige Gegenmaßnahmen autorisiert.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>This started an ongoing downward trend that is destroying capital values as we speak. As a response, the Global Trust board of directors and Sklyar Banes have authorized immediate measures to counter the threat of a global recession.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>This started an ongoing downward trend that is destroying capital values as we speak. As a response, the Global Trust board of directors and Sklyar Banes have authorized immediate measures to counter the threat of a global recession.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Ça a été le début d’une baisse progressive qui, en ce moment-même, détruit les valeurs en capital. En réaction, le conseil d’administration de Global Trust et Sklyar Banes ont autorisé des mesures immédiates pour contrer la menace de récession mondiale.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Ciò ha generato una tendenza al ribasso che sta distruggendo la capitalizzazione. In risposta, il consiglio d'amministrazione di Global Trust e Skylar Banes hanno autorizzato misure immediate per scongiurare una recessione globale.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Ciò ha generato una tendenza al ribasso che sta distruggendo la capitalizzazione. In risposta, il consiglio d'amministrazione di Global Trust e Skylar Banes hanno autorizzato misure immediate per scongiurare una recessione globale.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Esto ha desencadenado una continua tendencia a la baja que no para de destruir valores de capital. En respuesta, la Junta de directores de Global Trust y Skylar Banes han autorizado medidas inmediatas para combatir la amenaza de una recesión global.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Esto ha desencadenado una continua tendencia a la baja que no para de destruir valores de capital. En respuesta, la Junta de directores de Global Trust y Skylar Banes han autorizado medidas inmediatas para combatir la amenaza de una recesión global.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>To zapoczątkowało długotrwały trend spadkowy, który do tej pory szkodzi wartości kapitalizacji. W odpowiedzi, zarząd Global Trust i Sklyar Banes zaakceptowali natychmiastowe wdrożenie działań przeciwdziałających globalnej recesji.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>To zapoczątkowało długotrwały trend spadkowy, który do tej pory szkodzi wartości kapitalizacji. W odpowiedzi, zarząd Global Trust i Sklyar Banes zaakceptowali natychmiastowe wdrożenie działań przeciwdziałających globalnej recesji.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>To zahájilo recesi a Skylar Banesová s radou společnosti zareagovali přijetím protiopatření.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>To zahájilo recesi a Skylar Banesová s radou společnosti zareagovali přijetím protiopatření.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>В результате пошла устойчивая тенденция к снижению, и прямо сейчас наши активы продолжают обесцениваться. Совет директоров и лично Скайлар Бейнс уполномочили меня принять ряд шагов по предотвращению глобального экономического кризиса.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>В результате пошла устойчивая тенденция к снижению, и прямо сейчас наши активы продолжают обесцениваться. Совет директоров и лично Скайлар Бейнс уполномочили меня принять ряд шагов по предотвращению глобального экономического кризиса.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Dieser Kurssturz hat einen Abwärtstrend ausgelöst, der mit jeder Minute mehr Kapital vernichtet. Um eine weltweite Rezession zu verhindern, haben der Global Trust Vorstand und Skylar Banes sofortige Gegenmaßnahmen autorisiert.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Sequenz Audio+Text</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058057</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>world event 3 intro 03</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>trost</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-09-02 16:07</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>Seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-01-30 17:04</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Erstens: Wir möchten, dass Sie neue Bevölkerungszentren in den kürzlich aquirierten Sektoren aufbauen. Diese Siedlungen werden zeigen, dass wir weiter handlungsfähig sind und als stabile Einkommensquelle den wirtschaftlichen Abschwung auffangen.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Erstens: Wir möchten, dass Sie neue Bevölkerungszentren in den kürzlich aquirierten Sektoren aufbauen. Diese Siedlungen werden zeigen, dass wir weiter handlungsfähig sind und als stabile Einkommensquelle den wirtschaftlichen Abschwung auffangen.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>Measure number one: Contact all Architects. Global Trust wants you to develop new population centers in recently acquired sectors. These will serve as a show of strength and stable source of income to fight the economic downturn.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Mesure n°1 : contacter tous les architectes. Global Trust compte sur vous pour développer de nouveaux centres de peuplement dans les secteurs récemment acquis. Cela nous permettra de démontrer notre force ainsi que la stabilité de nos revenus en vue de combattre la crise économique.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Misura numero uno: contattare tutti gli architetti. Global Trust vuole che sviluppi nuovi centri per la Popolazione nei settori acquisiti di recente. Ciò mostrerà la nostra forza e garantirà una fonte di reddito stabile per contrastare la crisi economica.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Medida número uno: contactar con todos los arquitectos. Global Trust quiere que crees nuevos centros de población en sectores recién adquiridos. Servirán como demostración de fuerza y fuente estable de ingresos para combatir la recesión.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Działanie numer jeden: skontaktować się ze wszystkimi architektami. Global Trust zleca ci stworzenie nowych centrów populacji w niedawno zdobytych sektorach. To posłuży za pokaz siły i stabilne źródło przychodów do walki z kryzysem gospodarczym.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>První protiopatření: Kontaktovat všechny architekty. Global Trust chce zřídit nová města v nově získaných sektorech. Jejich výstavba pomůže stabilizovat ekonomiku.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Шаг первый: немедленно связаться со всеми архитекторами. Глобал Траст хочет, чтобы вы создали новые населенные пункты в недавно освоенных секторах. Это продемонстрирует, что у нас есть силы и стабильный доход для борьбы с экономическим спадом.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Erste Gegenmaßnahme: Alle Architekten kontaktieren. Global Trust möchte, dass Sie neue Bevölkerungszentren in kürzlich erworbenen Sektoren aufbauen. Diese Siedlungen werden zeigen, dass wir weiter handlungsfähig sind. Außerdem werden sie eine stabile Einkommensquelle um den wirtschaftlichen Abschwung aufzufangen.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Sequenz Audio+Text</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058058</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>world event 3 intro 04</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>trost</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-09-02 16:07</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>daniel.richter</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-10-04 19:03</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Zweites: Wir planen eine allgemeine Steuersenkung für Angestellte. Das wird Ihren Job schwieriger machen, aber dafür den Binnenmarkt langfristig gesund halten. Kompensieren Sie den Steuerverlust durch Expansion und konventionellen Handel.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Zweites: Wir planen eine allgemeine Steuersenkung für Angestellte. Das wird Ihren Job schwieriger machen, aber dafür den Binnenmarkt langfristig gesund halten. Kompensieren Sie den Steuerverlust durch Expansion und konventionellen Handel.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>Measure number two: A general reduction of employee tax rates. This makes your job slightly harder, but will keep the internal market healthy in the long run. Keep expanding and compensate the tax loss by conventional trading.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Mesure n°2 : réduction générale des taux d’imposition des employés. Cela risque de vous compliquer un peu la tâche mais, à long terme, la bonne santé du marché interne sera assurée. Poursuivez votre expansion et compensez les pertes fiscales par le commerce conventionnel.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Misura numero due: riduzione generale dell'aliquota fiscale degli impiegati. Questo ti renderà il lavoro più difficile, ma alla lunga gioverà al mercato interno. Continua a espanderti e compensa il calo delle Tasse con il commercio.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Medida dos: reducción general de impuestos a los trabajadores. Esto dificulta ligeramente tu trabajo, pero mantendrá en buen estado el mercado interior a largo plazo. Sigue expandiéndote y compensa la caída de impuestos mediante el comercio.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Działanie numer dwa: ogólne zmniejszenie stawek podatkowych dla pracujących. To trochę utrudni ci pracę, ale na dłuższą metę wzmocni rynek wewnętrzny. Kontynuuj rozwój i skompensuj straty podatkowe dobrym handlem.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Druhé protiopatření: Snížení daní zaměstnanců. Bude třeba více pracovat, ale posílí to trh. Ztráty na daních vykompenzuje územní expanze a zvýšení objemu obchodu.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Шаг второй: снижение всех налоговых ставок. Это несколько усложнит вам работу, но в долгосрочной перспективе укрепит внутренний рынок. Продолжайте экспансию и компенсируйте нехватку налогов посредством торговли.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Zweites: Eine allgemeine Steuersenkung für Angestellte. Das wird Ihren Job zwar ein schwieriger machen, aber dafür den Binnenmarkt langfristig gesund halten. Expandieren Sie weiter und kompensieren Sie den Steuerverlust durch konventionellen Handel.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Sequenz Audio+Text</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058059</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>world event 3 intro 05</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>trost</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-09-02 16:07</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-21 18:13</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Sie werden einige Zulieferer und ... andere Handelsgelegenheiten in Ihrem zugewiesenen Sektor vorfinden. Benutzen Sie diese zum gegenseitigen Vorteil. Enttäuschen Sie den Global Trust-Vorstand und vor allem unsere Angestellten nicht. Sie sehen zu Ihnen auf!</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Sie werden einige Zulieferer und ... andere Handelsgelegenheiten in Ihrem zugewiesenen Sektor vorfinden. Benutzen Sie diese zum gegenseitigen Vorteil. Enttäuschen Sie den Global Trust Vorstand und vor allem unsere Angestellten nicht. Sie sehen zu Ihnen auf!</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>You will find several subcontractors and ...other trading opportunities in your assigned sector. Use them for mutual benefit. Do not disappoint the Global Trust executives and above all, our employees. They look up to you!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Différents sous-traitants... ainsi que des opportunités commerciales vous attendent dans le secteur qui vous a été attribué. Tâchez d’en tirer un bénéfice mutuel. Ne décevez pas les dirigeants de Global Trust ni nos employés, car ils ont beaucoup d’estime pour vous !</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Nel settore che ti è stato assegnato, troverai numerosi collaboratori e... altre opportunità commerciali. Usali a beneficio tuo e nostro. Non deludere i dirigenti di Global Trust e, soprattutto, i nostri impiegati. Hanno fiducia in te!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Encontrarás a varios subcontratistas y... otras oportunidades de comercio en el sector asignado. Úsalos en beneficio mutuo. No decepciones a los ejecutivos de Global Trust y, sobre todo, a nuestros empleados. ¡Tienen sus esperanzas puestas en ti!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>W przydzielonym ci sektorze znajdziesz wielu podwykonawców i... inne możliwości handlowe. Wykorzystaj je dla obopólnych zysków. Nie rozczaruj zarządu Global Trust, a przede wszystkim pracowników. Oni na Ciebie liczą!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>V přiřazeném sektoru jistě najdete řadu subdodavatelů. Obchody s nimi budou jistě ku vzájemnému prospěchu. Rada  i lidé na vás spoléhají!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>В вашем секторе вы найдете несколько субподрядчиков; кроме того, там будут... и другие возможности для торговли. Постарайтесь обеспечить взаимную выгоду. Не подведите Глобал Траст, и, что самое важное - наших работников. Вы для них - пример!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Dieser Kurssturz hat einen Abwärtstrend ausgelöst, der mit jeder Minute mehr Kapital vernichtet. Um eine weltweite Rezession zu verhindern, haben der Global Trust Vorstand und Skylar Banes sofortige Gegenmaßnahmen autorisiert.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
          </Assets>
        </Group>
      </Groups>
      <Assets>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058000</GUID>
              <Kommentar>event title</Kommentar>
              <Creator>schneider</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-15 10:56</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2012-03-12 16:46</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>Global Distrust - Der große Börsencrash</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                </German>
                <English>
                  <Text>Global Distrust - The great stock market crash</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </English>
                <Polish>
                  <Text>Globalna nieufność - Wielki krach na rynku akcji</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Polish>
                <French>
                  <Text>Crise mondiale - Le grand krach boursier</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </French>
                <Italian>
                  <Text>Global Distrust - Il grande crollo in borsa</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Italian>
                <Spanish>
                  <Text>Crisis Mundial - El colapso de la bolsa</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Spanish>
                <Russian>
                  <Text>Кризис в "Глобал Траст"</Text>
                  <LastFinalText>Кризис в "Глобал Траст"</LastFinalText>
                  <Status>Final</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Russian>
                <Czech>
                  <Text>Globální nejistota - Velký krach na burze</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LastGermanText>Finanzkrise</LastGermanText>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058001</GUID>
              <Kommentar>mission 1 title</Kommentar>
              <Creator>schneider</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-15 10:56</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2012-03-20 14:51</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>Vertrauensbildende Maßnahme</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                </German>
                <English>
                  <Text>Confidence-building Measures</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </English>
                <Polish>
                  <Text>Środki budowy zaufania</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Polish>
                <French>
                  <Text>Mesures pour rétablir la confiance</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </French>
                <Italian>
                  <Text>Misure per ridare fiducia</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Italian>
                <Spanish>
                  <Text>Medidas de aumento de confianza</Text>
                  <LastFinalText>Medidas de aumento de confianza</LastFinalText>
                  <Status>Final</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Spanish>
                <Russian>
                  <Text>Антикризисное строительство</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Russian>
                <Czech>
                  <Text>Opatření pro uklidnění situace</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LastGermanText>Mission 01</LastGermanText>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058002</GUID>
              <Kommentar>mission 2 title</Kommentar>
              <Creator>schneider</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-15 10:56</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>Krisenintervention</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                </German>
                <English>
                  <Text>Crisis Intervention</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </English>
                <Polish>
                  <Text>Interwencja kryzysowa</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Polish>
                <French>
                  <Text>Intervention de crise</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </French>
                <Italian>
                  <Text>Intervento anticrisi</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Italian>
                <Spanish>
                  <Text>Intervención en la crisis</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Spanish>
                <Russian>
                  <Text>Предотвращение кризиса</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Russian>
                <Czech>
                  <Text>Krizová intervence</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LastGermanText>Mission 02</LastGermanText>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058003</GUID>
              <Creator>schneider</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-15 10:57</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>Freier Fall</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                </German>
                <English>
                  <Text>Freefall</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </English>
                <Polish>
                  <Text>Spadek</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Polish>
                <French>
                  <Text>Chute libre</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </French>
                <Italian>
                  <Text>Caduta libera</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Italian>
                <Spanish>
                  <Text>Caída libre</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Spanish>
                <Russian>
                  <Text>Свободное падение</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Russian>
                <Czech>
                  <Text>Volný pád</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LastGermanText>Mission 03</LastGermanText>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058004</GUID>
              <Kommentar>We 03 - Mission 01 short description</Kommentar>
              <Creator>petri</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-20 17:15</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2012-03-22 10:19</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Kleiner Sektor mit Bauland nahe Sokow Transnational.&lt;br /&gt;Einfacher Schwierigkeitsgrad&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                </German>
                <English>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Small sector with building land close to Sokow Transnational.&lt;br /&gt;Easy difficulty&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </English>
                <Polish>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Sektor ze zdatnym terenem do zabudowy, będący blisko Sokow Transnational.&lt;br /&gt;Niski poziom trudności.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <LastFinalText>&lt;p&gt;Sektor ze zdatnym terenem do zabudowy, będący blisko Sokow Transnational.&lt;br /&gt;Niski poziom trudności.&lt;/p&gt;</LastFinalText>
                  <Status>Final</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Polish>
                <French>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Petit secteur abritant des terrains constructibles proche de Sokow Transnational.&lt;br /&gt;Niveau Facile&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </French>
                <Italian>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Piccolo settore con terreno edificabile vicino a Sokow Transnational.&lt;br /&gt;Difficoltà facile&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Italian>
                <Spanish>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Sector pequeño con tierra edificable cerca de Sokow Transnational.&lt;br /&gt;Dificultad baja&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Spanish>
                <Russian>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Маленький сектор со стройплощадками неподалеку от "Соков Транснационал".&lt;br /&gt;Низкий уровень сложности&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Russian>
                <Czech>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Malý sektor s využitelnou půdou poblíž Sokow Transnational.&lt;br /&gt;Nízká obtížnost&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <LastFinalText>&lt;p&gt;Malý sektor s využitelnou půdou poblíž Sokow Transnational.&lt;br /&gt;Nízká obtížnost&lt;/p&gt;</LastFinalText>
                  <Status>Final</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LastGermanText>Kleiner Sektor mit Bauland nahe Sokow Transnational.&lt;br /&gt;Einfacher Schwierigkeitsgrad</LastGermanText>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058005</GUID>
              <Kommentar>We 03 - Mission 02 short description</Kommentar>
              <Creator>petri</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-20 17:15</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Mittlerer Sektor mit kleinen Handelsposten.&lt;br /&gt;Mittlerer Schwierigkeitsgrad&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                </German>
                <English>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Medium sector with small Trading posts.&lt;br /&gt;Medium difficulty&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </English>
                <Polish>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Średni sektor z niewielką ilością punktów handlowych.&lt;br /&gt;Średni poziom trudności&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Polish>
                <French>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Secteur de taille moyenne abritant de petits comptoirs commerciaux.&lt;br /&gt;Niveau Intermédiaire&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </French>
                <Italian>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Settore medio con piccoli Avamposti commerciali.&lt;br /&gt;Difficoltà media&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Italian>
                <Spanish>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Sector mediano con pequeños puestos comerciales.&lt;br /&gt;Dificultad media&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Spanish>
                <Russian>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Средний сектор с маленькими торговыми точками.&lt;br /&gt;Средний уровень сложности&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Russian>
                <Czech>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Střední sektor s malými centry obchodu.&lt;br /&gt;Střední obtížnost&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LastGermanText>Mittlerer Sektor mit kleinen Handelsposten.&lt;br /&gt;Mittlerer Schwierigkeitsgrad</LastGermanText>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058006</GUID>
              <Kommentar>We 03 - Mission 03 short description</Kommentar>
              <Creator>petri</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-20 17:15</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Großes Gebiet mit zahlreichen Frachtzentren&lt;br /&gt; Schwerer Schwierigkeitsgrad.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                </German>
                <English>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Large sector with numerous Trade centers&lt;br /&gt;Hard difficulty&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <LastFinalText>Destroy the Neo Skullz' headquarters. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is just a small outpost of these pirates. The located nuclear missiles are loosely guarded and not ready to be launched.</LastFinalText>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </English>
                <Polish>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Duży sektor z licznymi centrami handlowymi&lt;br /&gt;Wysoki poziom trudności&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Polish>
                <French>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Vaste secteur abritant de nombreux centres de commerce&lt;br /&gt;Niveau Difficile&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </French>
                <Italian>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Settore grande con numerosi Centri commerciali&lt;br /&gt;Difficoltà difficile&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Italian>
                <Spanish>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Sector grande con numerosos centros de comercio&lt;br /&gt;Dificultad alta&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Spanish>
                <Russian>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Большой сектор с множеством торговых центров&lt;br /&gt;Высокий уровень сложности&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Russian>
                <Czech>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Velký sektor s mnoha centry obchodu&lt;br /&gt;Vysoká obtížnost&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LastGermanText>Großes Gebiet mit zahlreichen Frachtzentren&lt;br /&gt; Schwerer Schwierigkeitsgrad.</LastGermanText>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058007</GUID>
              <Kommentar>We 03 - Mission 01 long description</Kommentar>
              <Creator>petri</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-20 17:54</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2012-03-14 15:01</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Siedeln Sie [GUIDNAME 1206002] an.&lt;br /&gt;Erwirtschaften Sie einige Credits durch Handel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ihre Einwohner erzeugen etwas weniger Steuereinnahmen. Es gibt einige Handelspartner in diesem Sektor. Finden Sie heraus, wo Sie die besten Angebote bekommen können.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                </German>
                <English>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Settle [GUIDNAME 1206002].&lt;br /&gt;Earn some Credits through Trade.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Residents generate a little less Tax income. There are a number of Trading partners in this Sector. Find out where to get the best deals.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <LastFinalText>Destroy the Neo Skullz' headquarters. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is just a small outpost of these pirates. The located nuclear missiles are loosely guarded and not ready to be launched.</LastFinalText>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </English>
                <Polish>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Osiedl się w: Fabrybudowniczowie.&lt;br /&gt;Zarób trochę kredytów na handlu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Twoi mieszkańcy przynoszą nieco mniejsze wpływy podatkowe. W tym sektorze znajduje się kilku partnerów handlowych. Zorientuj się, gdzie możesz zrobić najlepszy interes.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Polish>
                <French>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Installez des [GUIDNAME 1206002].&lt;br /&gt;Gagnez des crédits grâce au commerce.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vos résidents génèrent un peu moins de revenus fiscaux. Ce secteur abrite un certain nombre de partenaires commerciaux. Découvrez où conclure les meilleures affaires.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </French>
                <Italian>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Insedia [GUIDNAME 1206002].&lt;br /&gt;Guadagna Crediti con il commercio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I tuoi Residenti generano Entrate delle Tasse leggermente più basse. Questo settore offre vari Soci in affari. Cerca le occasioni più interessanti.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Italian>
                <Spanish>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Asienta [GUIDNAME 1206002].&lt;br /&gt;Consigue créditos a través del comercio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tus residentes generan un poco menos de impuestos. En este sector hay varios socios comerciales. Descubre dónde conseguir los mejores tratos.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Spanish>
                <Russian>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Заселите остров Бизнес-рабочими.&lt;br /&gt;Заработайте немного кредитов на торговле.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ваши жители платят чуть меньше налогов. В этом секторе много торговых партнеров - выясните, с кем выгоднее всего заключать сделки.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <LastFinalText>&lt;p&gt;Заселите остров Бизнес-рабочими.&lt;br /&gt;Заработайте немного кредитов на торговле.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ваши жители платят чуть меньше налогов. В этом секторе много торговых партнеров - выясните, с кем выгоднее всего заключать сделки.&lt;/p&gt;</LastFinalText>
                  <Status>Final</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Russian>
                <Czech>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Osídlete [GUIDNAME 1206002].&lt;br /&gt;Pomocí obchodování vydělejte nějaké kredity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vaši obyvatelé generují o něco nižší příjmy z daní. V tomto sektoru je několik potenciálních obchodních partnerů. Zjistěte, kde vám nabídnou nejlepší ceny.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LastGermanText>Siedeln Sie [GUIDNAME 1206002] an.&lt;br /&gt;Erwirtschaften Sie einige Credits durch Handel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ihre Einwohner erzeugen etwas weniger Steuereinnahmen. Es gibt einige Handelspartner in diesem Sektor. Finden Sie heraus, wo Sie die besten Angebote bekommen können.</LastGermanText>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058008</GUID>
              <Kommentar>We 03 - Mission 02 long description</Kommentar>
              <Creator>petri</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-20 17:54</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2012-03-14 15:02</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Siedeln Sie [GUIDNAME 1206101] an.&lt;br /&gt;Erwirtschaften Sie viele Credits durch Handel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ihre Einwohner erzeugen weniger Steuereinnahmen. Es gibt zahlreiche Handelspartner in diesem Sektor. Finden Sie heraus, wo Sie die besten Angebote bekommen können.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                </German>
                <English>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Settle [GUIDNAME 1206101].&lt;br /&gt;Earn a lot of Credits through Trade.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Residents generate less Tax income. There are a number of Trading partners in this Sector. Find out where to get the best deals.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <LastFinalText>Destroy the Neo Skullz' headquarters. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is just a small outpost of these pirates. The located nuclear missiles are loosely guarded and not ready to be launched.</LastFinalText>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </English>
                <Polish>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Osiedl się w: Fabryrobotnicy.&lt;br /&gt;Zarób dużo kredytów na handlu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Twoi mieszkańcy przynoszą mniejsze wpływy podatkowe. W tym sektorze znajduje się kilku partnerów handlowych. Zorientuj się, gdzie możesz zrobić najlepszy interes.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Polish>
                <French>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Installez des [GUIDNAME 1206101].&lt;br /&gt;Gagnez beaucoup de crédits grâce au commerce.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vos résidents génèrent moins de revenus fiscaux. Ce secteur abrite un certain nombre de partenaires commerciaux. Découvrez où conclure les meilleures affaires.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </French>
                <Italian>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Insedia [GUIDNAME 1206101].&lt;br /&gt;Guadagna molti Crediti con il commercio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I tuoi Residenti generano Entrate delle Tasse più basse. Questo settore offre vari Soci in affari. Cerca le occasioni più interessanti.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Italian>
                <Spanish>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Asienta [GUIDNAME 1206101].&lt;br /&gt;Consigue muchos créditos a través del comercio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tus residentes generan menos impuestos. En este sector hay varios socios comerciales. Descubre dónde conseguir los mejores tratos.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Spanish>
                <Russian>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Заселите остров Бизнес-инженерами.&lt;br /&gt;Заработайте большое количество кредитов на торговле.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ваши жители платят гораздо меньше налогов. В этом секторе есть несколько торговых партнеров - выясните, с кем выгоднее всего заключать сделки.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Russian>
                <Czech>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Osídlete [GUIDNAME 1206101].&lt;br /&gt;Pomocí obchodování vydělejte větší množství kreditů.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vaši obyvatelé generují nižší příjmy z daní. V tomto sektoru je několik potenciálních obchodních partnerů. Zjistěte, kde vám nabídnou nejlepší ceny.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LastGermanText>Siedeln Sie [GUIDNAME 1206101] an.&lt;br /&gt;Erwirtschaften Sie viele Credits durch Handel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ihre Einwohner erzeugen weniger Steuereinnahmen. Es gibt zahlreiche Handelspartner in diesem Sektor. Finden Sie heraus, wo Sie die besten Angebote bekommen können.</LastGermanText>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058009</GUID>
              <Kommentar>We 03 - Mission 03 long description</Kommentar>
              <Creator>petri</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-20 17:54</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2012-03-14 15:06</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Siedeln Sie [GUIDNAME 1206103] an.&lt;br /&gt;Erwirtschaften Sie sehr viele Credits durch Handel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ihre Einwohner erzeugen kaum noch Steuereinnahmen. Es gibt viele Handelspartner in diesem Sektor. Finden Sie heraus, wo Sie die besten Angebote bekommen können.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                </German>
                <English>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Settle [GUIDNAME 1206103].&lt;br /&gt;Earn a huge amount of Credits through Trade.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Residents generate hardly any Tax income. There are a number of Trading partners in this Sector. Find out where to get the best deals.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <LastFinalText>Destroy the Neo Skullz' headquarters. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is just a small outpost of these pirates. The located nuclear missiles are loosely guarded and not ready to be launched.</LastFinalText>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </English>
                <Polish>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Osiedl się w: Fabrykierownicy.&lt;br /&gt;Zarób mnóstwo kredytów na handlu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Twoi mieszkańcy przynoszą znikome wpływy podatkowe. W tym sektorze znajduje się kilku partnerów handlowych. Zorientuj się, gdzie możesz zrobić najlepszy interes.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Polish>
                <French>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Installez des [GUIDNAME 1206103].&lt;br /&gt;Faites fortune grâce au commerce.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vos résidents ne génèrent quasiment pas de revenus fiscaux. Ce secteur abrite un certain nombre de partenaires commerciaux. Découvrez où conclure les meilleures affaires.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </French>
                <Italian>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Insedia [GUIDNAME 1206103].&lt;br /&gt;Guadagna montagne di Crediti con il commercio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I tuoi Residenti generano Entrate delle Tasse quasi nulle. Questo settore offre vari Soci in affari. Cerca le occasioni più interessanti.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Italian>
                <Spanish>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Asienta [GUIDNAME 1206103].&lt;br /&gt;Consigue un montón de créditos a través del comercio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tus residentes apenas generan impuestos. En este sector hay varios socios comerciales. Descubre dónde conseguir los mejores tratos.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Spanish>
                <Russian>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Заселите остров Бизнес-управляющими.&lt;br /&gt;Заработайте огромное количество кредитов на торговле.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ваши жители почти не платят налогов. В этом секторе есть несколько торговых партнеров - выясните, с кем выгоднее всего заключать сделки.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <LastFinalText>&lt;p&gt;Заселите остров Бизнес-управляющими.&lt;br /&gt;Заработайте огромное количество кредитов на торговле.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ваши жители почти не платят налогов. В этом секторе есть несколько торговых партнеров - выясните, с кем выгоднее всего заключать сделки.&lt;/p&gt;</LastFinalText>
                  <Status>Final</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Russian>
                <Czech>
                  <Text>&lt;p&gt;Osídlete [GUIDNAME 1206103].&lt;br /&gt;Pomocí obchodování vydělejte obrovské množství kreditů.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vaši obyvatelé generují skoro nulové příjmy z daní. V tomto sektoru je několik potenciálních obchodních partnerů. Zjistěte, kde vám nabídnou nejlepší ceny.&lt;/p&gt;</Text>
                  <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                  <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LastGermanText>Siedeln Sie [GUIDNAME 1206103] an.&lt;br /&gt;Erwirtschaften Sie sehr viele Credits durch Handel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ihre Einwohner erzeugen kaum noch Steuereinnahmen. Es gibt viele Handelspartner in diesem Sektor. Finden Sie heraus, wo Sie die besten Angebote bekommen können.</LastGermanText>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
      </Assets>
    </Group>
    <Group>
      <Name>Quests</Name>
      <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
      <Groups>
        <Group>
          <Name>MainQuest Mission01</Name>
          <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
          <Assets>
            <Asset>
              <Template>CharacterText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058016</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>Queststarter Finanzkriese TEXT</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>petri</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-07-21 15:11</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] möchte, dass Sie verstärkt den Warenhandel ausbauen.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] wants you to increase your Trade in goods.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] prosi cię o zwiększenie twojego handlu towarami.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <French>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] vous demande d’augmenter vos échanges de marchandises.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] vuole che aumenti il tuo commercio di Merci.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] quiere que amplíes tu comercio de mercancías.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] хочет, чтобы вы повысили свой торговый товарооборот.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] po vás chce zvýšení objemu obchodu se zbožím.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] möchte, dass Sie mindestens [QUEST_PLAYERCOUNTER] [GUIDNAME 2600013] erwirtschaften.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>QuestText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058020</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>WIP - New Eden Queststatement braucht bezug zum Oilbaron und Rival</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>petri</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-07-21 15:45</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>„Wir mussten den neuen Siedlern leider Steuererleichterungen versprechen. Aber keine Sorge - sie werden moderat ausfallen. Trotzdem sollten Sie sich auf den Handel fokussieren."</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>"Unfortunately, we had to promise the new Settlers Tax cuts. But don't worry - they will be moderate. However, you should focus on Trade. "</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Niestety, musieliśmy obiecać nowym osadnikom ulgi podatkowe. Ale nie martw się - będą umiarkowane. Będzie jednak lepiej, jeśli skoncentrujesz się na handlu. </Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Nous avons malheureusement dû promettre des réductions fiscales aux nouveaux colons. Mais ne vous en faites pas, elles seront modérées. Vous devez toutefois vous concentrer sur le commerce. </Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Sfortunatamente, abbiamo dovuto promettere tagli alle Tasse ai Coloni. Ma non preoccuparti, saranno leggeri. Comunque, è meglio se ti concentri sul commercio. </Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Por desgracia, tuvimos que prometerles rebajas de impuestos a los nuevos habitantes. Pero no te preocupes, que serán moderadas. De todos modos, deberías centrarte en el comercio.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>К сожалению, нам пришлось пообещать новым поселенцам налоговые льготы. Но не беспокойтесь - льготы небольшие. Впрочем, лучше вам сосредоточиться на торговле.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Novým obyvatelům bylo nutné přislíbit snížení daní. Ale buďte bez obav - budeme si počínat obezřetně. Přesto by bylo vhodné začít se zabývat obchodem.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <LastGermanText>„Wir mussten den neuen Siedlern leider Steuererleichterungen versprechen. Aber keine Sorge - sie werden moderat ausfallen."</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Character Audio</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058026</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>Questreminder Finanzkriese</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>petri</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-07-25 17:31</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>Seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-01-30 17:04</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Sie sollten sich bei diesem Auftrag  nicht zuviel Zeit lassen. Global Trust hat eine Menge Marktanteile verloren, als die Eden Initiative einen neuen, sehr vielversprechenden Sektor gesperrt hat.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>You shouldn't take too much time over this task. Global Trust lost a large market share when the Eden Initiative blocked a new, very promising sector.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Cette mission ne devrait pas vous prendre trop de temps. Global Trust a perdu une part de marché importante lorsqu’Eden Initiative a bloqué un nouveau secteur très prometteur.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Non perdere troppo tempo con questo incarico. Global Trust ha perso un'importante fetta di mercato quando Eden Initiative ha bloccato un nuovo settore molto promettente.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>No deberías tardar mucho en terminar esta misión. Global Trust perdió una gran cuota de mercado cuando la Iniciativa Edén bloqueó un sector nuevo y prometedor.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Nie poświęcaj zbyt wiele czasu na to zadanie. Global Trust utracił sporą część udziałów rynkowych, gdy Eden Initiative zablokowało nowy, bardzo obiecujący sektor.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Nesmíte se zdržovat hloupostmi. Global Trust utrpěla značné ztráty, když Iniciativa Eden obsadila nový lukrativní sektor.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Не слишком-то медлите с этим заданием. Когда Эдем Инишиэйтив заблокировала новый многообещающий сектор, Глобал Траст потеряла крупную долю рынка.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Sie sollten sich nicht zuviel Zeit lassen bei diesen Auftrag. Diese New Eden sache hat Global Trust eine menge Geld gekostet.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
          </Assets>
        </Group>
        <Group>
          <Name>MainQuest Mission02</Name>
          <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
          <Assets>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Standard Text</Template>
              <Values>
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058017</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>Queststarter Finanzkriese TEXT</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>petri</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-07-21 15:41</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>mais</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-11-16 11:52</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <SubAssets />
                <TextTemplate />
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>[GUIDNAME 3058016]</Text>
                    </German>
                    <Czech>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LokaFlag>0</LokaFlag>
                  <LastGermanText>WIP - Finanzkriese Queststarter:&lt;br /&gt;[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] möchte das Sie mindestens [QUEST_PLAYERCOUNTER] [GUIDNAME 2600013] erwirtschaften.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
              <SubAssets>
                <SubAsset>
                  <ItemName>StandardHeader</ItemName>
                  <Values>
                    <Text>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </SubAsset>
                <SubAsset>
                  <ItemName>StandardBody</ItemName>
                  <Values>
                    <Text>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </SubAsset>
                <SubAsset>
                  <ItemName>DisabledHeader</ItemName>
                  <Values>
                    <Text>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </SubAsset>
                <SubAsset>
                  <ItemName>DisabledBody</ItemName>
                  <Values>
                    <Text>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </SubAsset>
                <SubAsset>
                  <ItemName>ActivatedHeader</ItemName>
                  <Values>
                    <Text>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </SubAsset>
                <SubAsset>
                  <ItemName>ActivatedBody</ItemName>
                  <Values>
                    <Text>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </SubAsset>
              </SubAssets>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>QuestText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058021</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>WIP - New Eden Queststatement braucht bezug zum Oilbaron und Rival</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>petri</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-07-21 15:53</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>„Die Steuererleichterungen für die neuen Siedler sind Teil der umfangreichen Kampagne von Global Trust. Sie müssen mit deutlichen Einbußen rechnen. Konzentrieren Sie sich daher auf den Handel."</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>"The Tax cuts for the new Settlers are part of the extensive Global Trust campaign. You have to expect significant losses. Focus therefore on Trade. "</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Ulgi podatkowe dla nowych osadników są częścią wielkiej kampanii Global Trust. Spodziewaj się poważnych niedoborów podatkowych. Dlatego już teraz skoncentruj się na handlu. </Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Les réductions fiscales offertes aux nouveaux colons font partie de la grande campagne de Global Trust. Pour compenser les lourdes pertes que vous risquez d’essuyer, concentrez-vous sur le commerce. </Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>I tagli alle Tasse per i nuovi Coloni fanno parte di una più ampia campagna di Global Trust. Ci attendiamo perdite significative. Perciò, concentrati sul commercio. </Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Las rebajas de impuestos para los nuevos habitantes forman parte de la amplia campaña de Global Trust. Debes esperar pérdidas significativas, por lo que tienes que centrarte en el comercio.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Налоговые льготы для новых поселенцев - это часть нашей глобальной программы. С доходами у вас будет туго, так что сосредоточьтесь на торговле.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Daňové úlevy pro nové osadníky jsou součástí rozsáhlé kampaně Global Trust. Musíte očekávat značné ztráty. Z toho důvodu se musíte soustředit na obchod.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <LastGermanText>„Die Steuererleichterungen für die neuen Siedler sind Teil der umfangreichen Kampagne von Global Trust. Sie müssen mit deutlichen Einbußen rechnen."</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
          </Assets>
        </Group>
        <Group>
          <Name>MainQuest Mission03</Name>
          <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
          <Assets>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Standard Text</Template>
              <Values>
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058018</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>Queststarter Finanzkriese TEXT</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>petri</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-07-21 15:41</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>mais</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-11-16 11:52</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <SubAssets />
                <TextTemplate />
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>[GUIDNAME 3058016]</Text>
                    </German>
                    <Czech>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LokaFlag>0</LokaFlag>
                  <LastGermanText>WIP - Finanzkriese Queststarter:&lt;br /&gt;[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] möchte das Sie mindestens [QUEST_PLAYERCOUNTER] [GUIDNAME 2600013] erwirtschaften.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
              <SubAssets>
                <SubAsset>
                  <ItemName>StandardHeader</ItemName>
                  <Values>
                    <Text>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </SubAsset>
                <SubAsset>
                  <ItemName>StandardBody</ItemName>
                  <Values>
                    <Text>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </SubAsset>
                <SubAsset>
                  <ItemName>DisabledHeader</ItemName>
                  <Values>
                    <Text>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </SubAsset>
                <SubAsset>
                  <ItemName>DisabledBody</ItemName>
                  <Values>
                    <Text>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </SubAsset>
                <SubAsset>
                  <ItemName>ActivatedHeader</ItemName>
                  <Values>
                    <Text>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </SubAsset>
                <SubAsset>
                  <ItemName>ActivatedBody</ItemName>
                  <Values>
                    <Text>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </SubAsset>
              </SubAssets>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>QuestText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058022</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>WIP - New Eden Queststatement braucht bezug zum Oilbaron und Rival</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>petri</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-07-21 15:59</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>"Das Siedlungsprogramm sagt den neuen Bewohnern erhebliche Steuererleichterungen zu. Versuchen Sie, Ihre Gewinne über den Warenhandel zu generieren."</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>The settlement program guarantees the new Residents substantial Tax cuts. Try to generate your profits through trading Goods.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Program osadnictwa gwarantuje nowym mieszkańcom spore ulgi podatkowe. Postaraj się zarabiać na handlu towarami.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Le programme de colonisation garantit des réductions fiscales substantielles aux nouveaux résidents. Essayez de générer des profits grâce au commerce.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Il programma d'insediamento garantisce dei notevoli tagli alle Tasse dei Residenti. Cerca di generare profitti commerciando Merci.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>El programa de asentamiento les garantiza a los nuevos residentes importantes rebajas de impuestos. Intenta generar tus beneficios comerciando mercancías.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Программа содействия поселенцам гарантирует им огромные налоговые льготы. Лучше постарайтесь заработать денег на продаже товаров.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Program pro osidlování garantuje novým osadníkům značné daňové úlevy. Pokuste se nahradit své ztráty pomocí obchodu.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <LastGermanText>Das Siedlungsprogramm sagt den neuen Bewohnern erhebliche Steuererleichterungen zu. Versuchen Sie, Ihre Gewinne über den Warenhandel zu generieren."</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
          </Assets>
        </Group>
        <Group>
          <Name>Additional Quests</Name>
          <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
          <DefaultTemplate>QuestText</DefaultTemplate>
          <Assets>
            <Asset>
              <Template>QuestText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058033</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-08 12:41</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>mais</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-11-16 11:52</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Sub Credits</Text>
                    </German>
                    <Czech>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <LokaFlag>0</LokaFlag>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>QuestText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058034</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-08 12:42</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>mais</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-11-16 11:52</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Sub Inhabitans</Text>
                    </German>
                    <Czech>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <LokaFlag>0</LokaFlag>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>QuestText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058035</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-08 13:36</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>mais</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-11-16 11:52</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Sub Credits</Text>
                    </German>
                    <Czech>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <LokaFlag>0</LokaFlag>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>QuestText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058036</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-08 13:36</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>mais</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-11-16 11:52</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Sub Credits</Text>
                    </German>
                    <Czech>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <LokaFlag>0</LokaFlag>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>QuestText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058037</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-08 13:36</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>mais</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-11-16 11:52</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Sub Inhabitans</Text>
                    </German>
                    <Czech>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <LokaFlag>0</LokaFlag>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>QuestText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058038</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-08 13:36</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>mais</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-11-16 11:52</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Sub Inhabitans</Text>
                    </German>
                    <Czech>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <LokaFlag>0</LokaFlag>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
          </Assets>
        </Group>
      </Groups>
    </Group>
    <Group>
      <Name>Mood</Name>
      <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
      <Groups>
        <Group>
          <Name>Tycoon</Name>
          <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
          <Assets>
            <Asset>
              <Template>CharacterText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058023</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>Spieler errichtet Stadtzentrum</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>petri</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-07-25 16:29</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] weist Sie nochmals auf die verminderten Steuereinkünfte durch die Bevölkerung hin.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] once again points out that your Population now generates less Tax income.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] jeszcze raz zauważa, że twoja populacja przynosi mniejsze wpływy podatkowe.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <French>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] relève une fois de plus que votre population génère moins de revenus fiscaux.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] segnala nuovamente che la tua Popolazione ora genera meno Entrate delle Tasse.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] vuelve a comentar que ahora tu población genera menos impuestos.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] снова отмечает, что ваше население сейчас платит меньше налогов.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] opět zdůrazňuje, že vaši obyvatelé produkují menší příjmy z daní.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Character Audio</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058024</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>Spieler errichtet Stadtzentrum - Audio</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>petri</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-07-25 16:33</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>daniel.richter</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-10-04 19:03</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Durch die Steuervergünstigungen sind die Einnahmen erheblich gemindert. Sie sollten sich auch nach anderen Einnahmequellen umsehen.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>The Tax incentives have significantly reduced our income, so you should look around for some other sources of revenue.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Les incitations fiscales ont fortement réduit nos recettes, ce qui va vous obliger à rechercher d’autres sources de revenus.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Gli incentivi fiscali hanno ridotto notevolmente il nostro reddito, quindi devi trovare altre fonti di guadagno.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Los incentivos fiscales han reducido notablemente nuestras ganancias, así que deberías buscar otras fuentes de ingresos.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Ulgi podatkowe znacząco obniżyły nasze przychody, więc rozejrzyj się za nowymi źródłami dochodu.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Daňové úlevy významně snížily naše příjmy. Musíte se poohlédnout po jiných zdrojích financí.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Налоговые новшества существенно снизили нашу прибыль, так что хорошо бы вам поискать другие источники дохода.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>CharacterText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058040</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 12:56</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] zeigt sich zuversichtlich.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] is confident.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] zachowuje pewność siebie.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <French>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] a confiance.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] ha fiducia.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] observa la situación con confianza.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] спокоен.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] si věří.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Character Audio</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058041</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 14:03</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>daniel.richter</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-10-04 19:03</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Die Turbulenzen an den Finanzmärkten können durch diese Kampagne ohne Probleme ausgeglichen werden. Sie haben das Vertrauen des Vorstands.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>The volatility of the financial markets can be offset if this campaign is successful. You have the full confidence of the board.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Si cette campagne aboutit, elle devrait compenser l’instabilité des marchés financiers. Le conseil d’administration vous accorde toute sa confiance.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>La volatilità dei mercati finanziari può essere compensata dal successo di questa campagna. Hai tutta la fiducia del consiglio d'amministrazione.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Si esta campaña tiene éxito podrá compensarse la volatilidad de los mercados financieros. La Junta confía plenamente en ti.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Zmienność rynków finansowych może być korzystna, jeśli ta kampania zakończy się powodzeniem. Masz pełne zaufanie zarządu.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Nestálosti finančních trhů je možné čelit, pokud bude tato o kampaň úspěšná. Máte plnou důvěru rady.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Если эта кампания завершится успехом, мы сможем компенсировать колебания рынка. Совет директоров полностью вас поддерживает.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Character Audio</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058042</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 14:05</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>Seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-01-30 17:04</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Nicht handlungsfähig? Wir werden dem Markt signalisieren, dass Global Trust mächtig wie eh und je ist.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>Incapable of action? We'll send out a clear signal to the market that Global Trust is as powerful as ever.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Impossible d’agir ? Nous allons adresser un signal clair aux marchés afin qu’ils comprennent que Global Trust est plus puissant que jamais.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Incapaci di agire? Manderemo un chiaro segnale al mercato che la Global Trust è più potente che mai.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>¿No puedes hacer nada? Enviaremos una señal clara al mercado de que Global Trust es tan poderoso como siempre.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Niezdolni do działania? Damy rynkowi wyraźny sygnał, że Global Trust nigdy nie było silniejsze.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Neschopní akce? Vyšleme trhům jasnou zprávu, že Global Trust je pořád při síle!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Неспособны действовать? Мы четко дадим рынку понять, что Глобал Траст сильна как никогда.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Character Audio</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058043</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 14:08</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>daniel.richter</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-10-04 19:03</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Diese Siedlungskampagne ist durch geringere Steuereinnahmen zwar investitionsintensiv, aber das Kapital, dass sich aus Gütern und neuen Siedlern aquirieren lässt, ist gewaltig.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>While the reduced Tax income makes this Settlement campaign somewhat more investment-intensive than usual, the potential Capital to be earned from Goods and new Settlers is simply enormous.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>3</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Compte tenu de la réduction des revenus fiscaux, cette campagne de colonisation nécessite davantage d’investissements que d’habitude, mais les bénéfices que peuvent rapporter les marchandises et les nouveaux colons en termes de capital sont énormes.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Con Entrate delle tasse ridotte, occorrerà investire di più per questa campagna d'Insediamento, ma il Capitale che si può ricavare dalle Merci e dai nuovi Coloni è davvero enorme.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Aunque la reducción de ingresos fiscales hace que esta campaña de colonización sea más difícil de financiar de lo normal, la ganancia potencial proveniente de las mercancías y los nuevos pobladores es enorme.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Zmniejszone wpływy podatkowe sprawiają, że ta kampania zasiedleniowa będzie wymagała większych inwestycji, ale potencjalne zyski z towarów i nowych osadników są olbrzymie.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>I když to snížení daní vyžaduje vyšší investice při osidlování nových území, potenciální zisky jsou astronomické.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Несмотря на то, что из-за налоговых льгот это поселение требует куда больше вложений, чем обычно, потенциальный доход от товаров и новых жителей просто огромен.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Diese Siedlungskampagne ist durch geringere Steuereinnahmen zwar investitionsintensiv, aber das Kapital, dass sich aus Gütern und neuen Siedlern schlagen lässt, ist gewaltig.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Character Audio</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058044</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 14:26</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>Seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-01-30 17:04</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Die Technologien der Eden Initiative sind gerade sehr gefragt - aber das werden wir ändern.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>The Technologies of the Eden Initiative are in great demand - we'll change all that.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Les technologies d’Eden Initiative connaissent une forte demande. Nous allons changer tout ça.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Le Tecnologie dell'Eden Initiative sono molto richieste. Faremo in modo che questo cambi.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Las tecnologías de la Iniciativa Edén tiene mucha demanda. Eso lo cambiaremos.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Technologie Eden Initiative cieszą się wielką popularnością - zmienimy to.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Technologie Iniciativy Eden jsou velmi žádané - musíme to změnit.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Технологии Эдем Инишиэйтив пользуются огромным спросом - но мы это исправим.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Die Technologien der Eden Initiative sind gerade sehr gefragt - das werden wir ändern.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Character Audio</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058045</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 14:31</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-01-31 10:59</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Global Trust ist immer noch das exportstärkste Unternehmen am Markt. Wenn wir uns auf etwas verlassen können, dann auf unsere wirtschaftlichen Beziehungen.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Global Trust ist immer noch das exportstärkste Unternehmen am Markt. Wenn wir uns auf etwas verlassen können, dann auf unsere wirtschaftlichen Beziehungen.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>Global Trust is the strongest company in the market in terms of exports. If there's one thing we can rely on, it's our commercial activities.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Global Trust is the strongest company in the market in terms of exports. If there's one thing we can rely on, it's our commercial activities.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Global Trust est la première compagnie exportatrice du marché. S’il y a bien une chose sur laquelle on peut compter, c’est notre activité commerciale.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Global Trust è la Compagnia più forte sul mercato per quanto riguarda le esportazioni. Se c'è una cosa su cui possiamo contare, sono le nostre attività commerciali.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Global Trust è la Compagnia più forte sul mercato per quanto riguarda le esportazioni. Se c'è una cosa su cui possiamo contare, sono le nostre attività commerciali.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Global Trust es la compañía más fuerte del mercado en cuanto a exportaciones. Si hay algo en lo que confiar, son nuestras actividades comerciales.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Global Trust es la compañía más fuerte del mercado en cuanto a exportaciones. Si hay algo en lo que confiar, son nuestras actividades comerciales.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Global Trust to pod względem eksportu najsilniejsza firma na rynku. Zawsze możemy polegać na naszych działaniach handlowych.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Global Trust to pod względem eksportu najsilniejsza firma na rynku. Zawsze możemy polegać na naszych działaniach handlowych.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Global Trust je největším exportérem zboží na trhu. Pokud se na něco můžeme spolehnout, pak jsou to naše obchodní aktivity.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Global Trust je největším exportérem zboží na trhu. Pokud se na něco můžeme spolehnout, pak jsou to naše obchodní aktivity.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Глобал Траст - крупнейшая экспортная компания на рынке. Если на что-то можно положиться, так это на нашу коммерческую деятельность.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Глобал Траст - крупнейшая экспортная компания на рынке. Если на что-то можно положиться, так это на нашу коммерческую деятельность.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Global Trust ist immer noch das exportsträkste Unternehmen am Markt. Wenn wir uns auf etwas verlassen könnnen, dann auf unsere wirtschaftlichen Beziehungen.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
          </Assets>
        </Group>
        <Group>
          <Name>Trenchcoat</Name>
          <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
          <Assets>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Character Audio</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058025</GUID>
                  <Kommentar>Trenchcoat betritt zum ersten Mal die Welt - nachfolgend werden Standardmeldungen genutzt</Kommentar>
                  <Creator>petri</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-07-25 16:57</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>Seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-01-30 17:04</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Hatte ich ja mal wieder den richtigen Riecher! Wo Global Trust 'nen neuen Sektor erschließt, gibt's eben immer Potenzial für gute Geschäfte.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>Yet again, I just knew it! There's always good business to be had where Global Trust opens up a new sector.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Oui, je le savais ! Quand Global Trust ouvre un nouveau secteur, ça sent les bonnes affaires.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Me lo aspettavo, come al solito! Quando Global Trust apre un nuovo settore c'è sempre da fare dei buoni affari.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>¡Otra vez, lo sabía! Siempre hay buenas oportunidades de negocio cuando Global Trust abre un nuevo sector.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>No i znowu wiedziałem od razu! Jak tylko Global Trust otwiera nowy sektor, zawsze będzie jakiś dobry interes do zrobienia.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Já to věděl! Kdykoliv Global Trust obsadí nový sektor, obchody vzkvétají.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Как всегда - я так и знал! Когда Глобал Траст открывает новый сектор, это всегда к доброй торговле.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330001</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Ah, hatten meine Informanten also wieder mal recht! Eine neue Gegend für gute Geschäfte. Kommt ran An- und Verkauf zu besten Preisen.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>CharacterText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058039</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-08 14:55</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] hat seine Preise angepasst und bietet sich als besonders lukrativer Handelspartner an.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] has adjusted their prices and is therefore a very lucrative Trading partner.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] dostosowuje ceny, przez co staje się bardzo dobrym partnerem handlowym.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <French>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] a revu ses prix. Il s’agit désormais d’un partenaire commercial très lucratif.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] ha ritoccato i prezzi, perciò è un Socio in affari molto appetibile.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] ha ajustado sus precios, por lo que ahora es un socio comercial muy lucrativo.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] снизил цены и потому может стать очень перспективным торговым партнером.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] upravuje svoje ceny a je proto lukrativním obchodním partnerem.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330001</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Trenchcoat ist besonders an guten Geschäften mit Ihnen interessiert und hat daher seine Ein- und Verkaufspreise angepasst.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
          </Assets>
        </Group>
        <Group>
          <Name>Devi</Name>
          <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
          <Assets>
            <Asset>
              <Template>CharacterText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058046</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 14:39</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] setzt im Konflikt zwischen Global Trust und der Eden Initiative auf Zurückhaltung.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] is exercising restraint in the conflict between Global Trust and the Eden Initiative.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] zachowuje się powściągliwie w sprawie konfliktu między Global Trust i Eden Initiative.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <French>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] fait preuve de mesure dans le conflit entre Global Trust et Eden Initiative.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] agisce con moderazione nello scontro tra Global Trust e Eden Initiative.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] se está comidiendo en el conflicto entre Global Trust y la Iniciativa Edén.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] придерживается нейтралитета в конфликте между "Глобал Траст" и "Эдем Инишиэйтив".</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] se do konfliktu mezi Global Trust a Iniciativou Eden snaží nezapojovat.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330004</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] hält sich im Konflikt zwischen Global Trust und der Eden Initiative zurück.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>CharacterText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058047</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 14:43</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Ich sehe bereits den Konflikt zwischen der Eden Initiative und Global Trust aufziehen. S.A.A.T. wird sich in dieser Angelegenhet passiv verhalten.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>I can already see conflict coming between the Eden Initiative and Global Trust. S.A.A.T. will remain passive in this matter.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Wiem, że wkrótce wybuchnie konflikt między Eden Initiative i Global Trust. S.A.A.T. zachowa neutralność w tej sprawie.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Je vois déjà poindre un conflit entre Eden Initiative et Global Trust. S.A.A.T. préfère rester neutre dans cette affaire.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Vedo già uno scontro tra Eden Initiative e Global Trust all'orizzonte. La S.A.A.T. resterà neutrale in questa faccenda.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Veo que se avecina un conflicto entre la Iniciativa Edén y Global Trust. La S.A.A.T. se quedará al margen de este asunto.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Я уже предвижу схватку между "Эдем Инишиэйтив" и "Глобал Траст". НАУК по этому вопросу останется в стороне.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Konflikt mezi Iniciativou Eden a Global Trust je na spadnutí. S.A.A.T. se do něj nezapojí.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330004</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Ich sehe bereits einen Konflikt zwischen der Eden Initiative und Global Trust am aufziehen. S.A.A.T. wird sich in dieser angelegenhet passiv verhalten.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>CharacterText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058048</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 14:47</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>S.A.A.T. folgt einzig und allein der Logik und wissenschaftlichen Bestrebungen. Daher sind wir in solche Streitigkeiten auch nicht involviert.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>S.A.A.T. is solely dedicated to logic and the pursuit of scientific endeavor. We are therefore never involved in these conflicts.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>S.A.A.T. kieruje się wyłącznie logiką i zajmuje się przedsięwzięciami naukowymi. Dlatego nigdy nie mieszamy się w takie konflikty.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <French>
                      <Text>S.A.A.T. se consacre uniquement à la logique et à la science, d’où sa distance vis-à-vis de ces conflits.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Il solo obiettivo della S.A.A.T. è lo sviluppo della logica e delle scoperte scientifiche. Perciò, non ci facciamo mai coinvolgere in questi conflitti.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>La S.A.A.T. se dedica únicamente a la lógica y al conocimiento científico. Por lo tanto, nunca nos involucramos en estos conflictos.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Сотрудники НАУК посвятили свою жизнь разуму и научным открытиям. В такие конфликты мы никогда не лезем.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>S.A.A.T. postupuje čistě logicky a jediným naším zájmem je věda. Do takovýchto konfliktů se proto nikdy nezapojujeme.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330004</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>S.A.A.T. folgt einzig und allein der Logik und wissenschaftlichen Bestrebungen, daher sind wir in solche Streitigkeiten auch nicht involviert.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
          </Assets>
        </Group>
        <Group>
          <Name>Sokow</Name>
          <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
          <Assets>
            <Asset>
              <Template>CharacterText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058049</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 14:49</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] ist von den finanziellen Turbulenzen schwer betroffen.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] is severely affected by the financial turmoil.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] poważnie odczuwa skutki kryzysu finansowego.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <French>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] subit de plein fouet la crise financière.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] ha subito gravi perdite per le incertezze finanziarie.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>A [THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] le ha afectado mucho toda esta agitación financiera.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] сильно пострадал от финансового кризиса.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] se dostává kvůli komplikacím na finančních trzích do potíží.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330021</SprecherAuswahl>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Character Audio</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058050</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 14:51</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>Seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-01-30 17:04</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Ich bin an guten Geschäften interessiert - an mehr nicht. Aber die Eden Initiative hat mein Unternehmen in die Miesen gerissen.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>I'm interested in good business and quick profits, and that's it. The Eden Initiative has dragged my company down into the quagmire.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Ce qui m’intéresse, ce sont les bonnes affaires et les profits rapides, c’est tout. Eden Initiative a entraîné ma compagnie dans un véritable bourbier.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Quello che mi interessa sono i buoni affari e i profitti veloci, punto. È la Eden Initiative che ha trascinato la mia compagnia in questa palude.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>Me interesan los buenos negocios y el beneficio rápido, punto. La Iniciativa Edén ha arrastrado a mi compañía a un lodazal.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Interesują mnie wyłącznie dobre interesy i szybkie zyski. Przez Eden Initiative moja firma znalazła się w niezłym bagnie.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Zajímají mě dobré rychlé obchody. Iniciativa Eden mi jen hází klacky pod nohy.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Меня интересует хороший бизнес и быстрая прибыль - вот и все. Эдем Инишиэйтив связала нас по рукам и ногам.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330021</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Ich bin an guten Geschäften und schnellem Profit interessiert - an mehr nicht. Die Eden Initiative hat mein Unternehmen in die Miesen gerissen.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Character Audio</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058051</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 15:05</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>daniel.richter</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2011-10-04 19:04</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Nur Profit spielt eine Rolle - nicht irgendwelche grünen Bäume! Man muss den Leuten wieder ins Gedächtnis rufen, was ihnen den Wohlstand gebracht hat. </Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>Money is what matters, not some clump of old green trees! We have to remind people about what made them so prosperous!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Ce qui compte, c’est l’argent, pas ces vieux arbres ! Il serait temps que les gens se souviennent de ce qui a fait leur prospérité !</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>Sono i soldi che contano, non un paio di vecchi tronchi verdi! Dobbiamo ricordare alla gente da dove proviene la sua prosperità!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>¡Lo que importa es el dinero, no un montón de árboles viejos! ¡Debemos recordarle a la gente qué les llevó a ser tan prósperos!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Liczą się pieniądze, a nie kupa starych zielonych drzew! Musimy przypomnieć ludziom co sprawiło, że dobrze im się powodzi!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Jde tu o peníze, ne nějaké bezvýznamné stromy! Musíme lidem připomenout, kdo je dostal na vrchol!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Деньги - вот что важно, а не кучка каких-то старых деревьев! Мы должны напомнить людям, что привело их к процветанию!</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330021</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText> Geld ist es, was eine Rolle spielt und nicht irgendwelche grünen Bäume! Wir müssen den Leuten wieder ins Gedächtnis rufen, was ihnen den Wohlstand gebracht hat. </LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
          </Assets>
        </Group>
        <Group>
          <Name>Yana</Name>
          <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
          <Assets>
            <Asset>
              <Template>CharacterText</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058052</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 15:06</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] sieht sich durch die Krise bei den Tycoons bestätigt.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] sees their philosophy confirmed by the Tycoons' crisis.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] uważa, że słuszność ich filozofii została potwierdzona kryzysem Fabrytów.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <French>
                      <Text>La crise que traversent les Tycoons confirme la philosophie de [THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER].</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] vede una conferma della sua filosofia nella crisi Tycoon.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] observa cómo la crisis de los tycoons confirma su filosofía.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] видит в кризисе подтверждение своей философии.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] vidí v krizi Magnátů potvrzení správnosti své filozofie.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330002</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] hält sich im Konflikt zwischen Global Trust und der Eden Initiative zurück.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Character Audio</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058053</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 15:14</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>Seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-01-30 17:04</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Die Menschen beginnen endlich die Augen zu öffnen! Nachhaltigkeit ist gefragt, Zerstörung der Umwelt verpönt. Global Trust wird sich diesem Zeitgeist unterwerfen müssen.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>People are starting to open their eyes! Sustainability is what's wanted; destruction of the environment is frowned upon. Global Trust will have to accept and follow the zeitgeist.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Les gens commencent à ouvrir les yeux ! Ils sont sensibles au développement durable et voient d’un très mauvais œil les atteintes portées à l’environnement. Global Trust va bien devoir l’accepter et suivre le mouvement.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>La gente comincia ad aprire gli occhi! Cerca la sostenibilità e critica la distruzione dell'ambiente. Global Trust dovrà accettarlo e adeguarsi ai tempi.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>¡La gente empieza a abrir los ojos! Quieren sostenibilidad; rechazan la destrucción del medioambiente. Global Trust deberá aceptarlo y unirse a la tendencia actual.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Ludzie wreszcie zaczynają otwierać oczy! Każdy pragnie równowagi ekologicznej, nikomu nie podoba się niszczenie środowiska. Global Trust musi się z tym pogodzić i iść z duchem czasu.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Lidem to konečně začíná docházet! Ničení životního prostředí nikam nevede. Global Trust to bude muset přijmout a jít s dobou.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>У людей открылись глаза! Все говорят о разумном использовании ресурсов, никто не готов мириться с разрушением окружающей среды. Глобал Траст теперь придется действовать в духе времени.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330002</SprecherAuswahl>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
            <Asset>
              <Template>Character Audio</Template>
              <Values>
                <Sound />
                <Standard>
                  <GUID>3058054</GUID>
                  <Creator>zellmann</Creator>
                  <CreationTime>2011-08-22 15:18</CreationTime>
                  <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                  <LastChangeTime>2012-01-31 10:59</LastChangeTime>
                </Standard>
                <Text>
                  <LocaText>
                    <German>
                      <Text>Ein ganz neues Umweltbewusstsein hat sich in die Köpfe der Menschen gesetzt. Auch die neue Propaganda-Kampagne von Global Trust wird das nicht mehr ändern können.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Ein ganz neues Umweltbewusstsein hat sich in die Köpfe der Menschen gesetzt. Auch die neue Propaganda-Kampagne von Global Trust wird das nicht mehr ändern können.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </German>
                    <English>
                      <Text>People have opened themselves up to a whole new level of environmental awareness. And Global Trust's new propaganda campaign can do nothing to reverse the trend.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>People have opened themselves up to a whole new level of environmental awareness. And Global Trust's new propaganda campaign can do nothing to reverse the trend.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </English>
                    <French>
                      <Text>Les gens ont pris conscience de l’importance de protéger l’environnement. Et la nouvelle campagne de propagande lancée par Global Trust ne parviendra, en aucun cas, à inverser la tendance.</Text>
                      <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </French>
                    <Italian>
                      <Text>La gente ha raggiunto un nuovo livello di consapevolezza ambientale. E la nuova campagna pubblicitaria di Global Trust non basterà certo per invertire la tendenza.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>La gente ha raggiunto un nuovo livello di consapevolezza ambientale. E la nuova campagna pubblicitaria di Global Trust non basterà certo per invertire la tendenza.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Italian>
                    <Spanish>
                      <Text>La gente ha aceptado un nuevo nivel de conciencia medioambiental. Y la nueva campaña publicitaria de Global Trust es incapaz de revertir la tendencia.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>La gente ha aceptado un nuevo nivel de conciencia medioambiental. Y la nueva campaña publicitaria de Global Trust es incapaz de revertir la tendencia.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Spanish>
                    <Polish>
                      <Text>Ludzie są gotowi na nowy poziom świadomości ekologicznej. A nowa kampania propagandowa Global Trust nie odmieni tego trendu.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Ludzie są gotowi na nowy poziom świadomości ekologicznej. A nowa kampania propagandowa Global Trust nie odmieni tego trendu.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Polish>
                    <Czech>
                      <Text>Lidé pochopili a propaganda Global Trust se začíná míjet účinkem.</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Lidé pochopili a propaganda Global Trust se začíná míjet účinkem.</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Czech>
                    <Russian>
                      <Text>Люди наконец-то по-настоящему прониклись своей ответственностью перед окружающей средой. И даже пропаганда Глобал Траст этого не изменит!</Text>
                      <LastFinalText>Люди наконец-то по-настоящему прониклись своей ответственностью перед окружающей средой. И даже пропаганда Глобал Траст этого не изменит!</LastFinalText>
                      <Status>Final</Status>
                      <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                    </Russian>
                  </LocaText>
                  <SprecherAuswahl>2330002</SprecherAuswahl>
                  <LastGermanText>Ein ganz neues Umweltbewusstsein hat sich in die Köpfe der Menschen gesetzt. Auch die neue Propaganda-Kampagne von Global Trust wird das nicht mehr ändern könnnen.</LastGermanText>
                </Text>
              </Values>
            </Asset>
          </Assets>
        </Group>
      </Groups>
    </Group>
    <Group>
      <Name>Sequences</Name>
      <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
      <Groups>
        <Group>
          <Name>Intro</Name>
          <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
          <Groups>
            <Group>
              <Name>EVE</Name>
              <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
            </Group>
            <Group>
              <Name>Rufus</Name>
              <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
              <Assets>
                <Asset>
                  <Template>Standard Text</Template>
                  <Values>
                    <Standard>
                      <GUID>3058027</GUID>
                      <Kommentar>WE3 Intro</Kommentar>
                      <Creator>petri</Creator>
                      <CreationTime>2011-07-26 14:17</CreationTime>
                      <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                      <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                    </Standard>
                    <SubAssets />
                    <TextTemplate />
                    <Text>
                      <LocaText>
                        <German>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] erläutert Ihnen kurz die aktuelle Lage.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                        </German>
                        <English>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] briefly explains the current situation.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </English>
                        <Polish>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] krótko objaśnia aktualną sytuację.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Polish>
                        <French>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] explique brièvement la situation actuelle.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </French>
                        <Italian>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] spiega rapidamente la situazione attuale.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Italian>
                        <Spanish>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] explica brevemente la situación actual.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Spanish>
                        <Russian>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] вкратце объясняет текущую ситуацию.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Russian>
                        <Czech>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] ve zkratce vysvětluje aktuální situaci.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Czech>
                      </LocaText>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                      <LastGermanText>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] weist Sie auf die Wichtigkeit dieser Mission hin.</LastGermanText>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </Asset>
                <Asset>
                  <Template>Character Audio</Template>
                  <Values>
                    <Sound />
                    <Standard>
                      <GUID>3058028</GUID>
                      <Kommentar>WE3 Intro - Rufus Meldung AUDIO Mission01</Kommentar>
                      <Creator>petri</Creator>
                      <CreationTime>2011-07-26 14:19</CreationTime>
                      <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                      <LastChangeTime>2012-01-31 10:48</LastChangeTime>
                    </Standard>
                    <Text>
                      <LocaText>
                        <German>
                          <Text>Dieser Sektor ist ideal für eine wirtschaftliche Erschließung. Wir erwarten von Ihnen, diese Aufgabe trotz der widrigen Umstände professionell abzuwickeln.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Dieser Sektor ist ideal für eine wirtschaftliche Erschließung. Wir erwarten von Ihnen, diese Aufgabe trotz der widrigen Umstände professionell abzuwickeln.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                        </German>
                        <English>
                          <Text>This sector is ideal for economic development. We expect you to handle the job professionally, despite the adverse circumstances.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>This sector is ideal for economic development. We expect you to handle the job professionally, despite the adverse circumstances.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>3</ExportCount>
                        </English>
                        <French>
                          <Text>Ce secteur est idéal pour le développement économique. Malgré les circonstances, nous comptons sur votre professionnalisme.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </French>
                        <Italian>
                          <Text>Questo settore è ideale per lo sviluppo economico. Ci aspettiamo che tu faccia un buon lavoro, nonostante le circostanze avverse.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Questo settore è ideale per lo sviluppo economico. Ci aspettiamo che tu faccia un buon lavoro, nonostante le circostanze avverse.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Italian>
                        <Spanish>
                          <Text>Este sector es idóneo para el desarrollo económico. Esperamos que hagas el trabajo profesionalmente a pesar de las circunstancias adversas.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Este sector es idóneo para el desarrollo económico. Esperamos que hagas el trabajo profesionalmente a pesar de las circunstancias adversas.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Spanish>
                        <Polish>
                          <Text>Ten sektor jest idealny do rozwoju gospodarczego. Spodziewamy się, że wykonasz to zadanie profesjonalnie, niezależnie od niesprzyjających okoliczności.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Ten sektor jest idealny do rozwoju gospodarczego. Spodziewamy się, że wykonasz to zadanie profesjonalnie, niezależnie od niesprzyjających okoliczności.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Polish>
                        <Czech>
                          <Text>Tento sektor je dokonalý pro ekonomický rozvoj. Očekáváme, že se toho úspěšně zhostíte i přes ztížené podmínky.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Tento sektor je dokonalý pro ekonomický rozvoj. Očekáváme, že se toho úspěšně zhostíte i přes ztížené podmínky.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Czech>
                        <Russian>
                          <Text>Этот сектор идеально подходит для развития экономики. Мы рассчитываем, что вы будете действовать как профессионал, невзирая на любые возможные обстоятельства.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Этот сектор идеально подходит для развития экономики. Мы рассчитываем, что вы будете действовать как профессионал, невзирая на любые возможные обстоятельства.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Russian>
                      </LocaText>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                      <LastGermanText>Dieser Sektor erwartet seine wirtschaftliche Erschließung. Wir erwarten von Ihnen, diese Aufgabe trotz der widrigen Umstände professionell abzuwickeln.</LastGermanText>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </Asset>
                <Asset>
                  <Template>Character Audio</Template>
                  <Values>
                    <Sound />
                    <Standard>
                      <GUID>3058060</GUID>
                      <Kommentar>WE3 Intro - Rufus Meldung AUDIO Mission02</Kommentar>
                      <Creator>bombera</Creator>
                      <CreationTime>2011-09-07 21:21</CreationTime>
                      <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                      <LastChangeTime>2012-01-31 10:48</LastChangeTime>
                    </Standard>
                    <Text>
                      <LocaText>
                        <German>
                          <Text>Betrachten Sie es als Ehre, dass Sie ganz alleine für diesen großen Sektor verantwortlich sind. Die Firma hat großes Vertrauen in Ihre Fähigkeiten.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Betrachten Sie es als Ehre, dass Sie ganz alleine für diesen großen Sektor verantwortlich sind. Die Firma hat großes Vertrauen in Ihre Fähigkeiten.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                        </German>
                        <English>
                          <Text>Consider it an honor that you alone are responsible for a sector this large. The company has great confidence in your abilities.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Consider it an honor that you alone are responsible for a sector this large. The company has great confidence in your abilities.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>2</ExportCount>
                        </English>
                        <French>
                          <Text>Considérez comme un honneur d’endosser seul la responsabilité d’un aussi vaste secteur. La compagnie croit beaucoup en vos talents.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </French>
                        <Italian>
                          <Text>Considera un onore che ti sia affidata la responsabilità di un settore così ampio. La Compagnia ha piena fiducia nelle tue capacità.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Considera un onore che ti sia affidata la responsabilità di un settore così ampio. La Compagnia ha piena fiducia nelle tue capacità.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Italian>
                        <Spanish>
                          <Text>Considera un honor que tú solo seas responsable de un sector tan grande. La compañía confía mucho en tu capacidad.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Considera un honor que tú solo seas responsable de un sector tan grande. La compañía confía mucho en tu capacidad.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Spanish>
                        <Polish>
                          <Text>Uznaj za zaszczyt fakt, że w pojedynkę odpowiadasz za tak duży sektor. Firma wierzy w twoje umiejętności.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Uznaj za zaszczyt fakt, że w pojedynkę odpowiadasz za tak duży sektor. Firma wierzy w twoje umiejętności.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Polish>
                        <Czech>
                          <Text>Je to pro vás čest, že zodpovídáte za tak velký sektor. Společnost plně důvěřuje vašim schopnostem.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Je to pro vás čest, že zodpovídáte za tak velký sektor. Společnost plně důvěřuje vašim schopnostem.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Czech>
                        <Russian>
                          <Text>Считайте, что это огромная честь - вы в одиночку отвечаете за такой крупный сектор. Компания верит в вас.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Считайте, что это огромная честь - вы в одиночку отвечаете за такой крупный сектор. Компания верит в вас.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Russian>
                      </LocaText>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                      <LastGermanText>Was für eine Ehre! Sie haben diesen großen Sektor ganz alleine zugewiesen bekommen. Die Firma hat großes Vertrauen in Ihre Fertigkeiten.</LastGermanText>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </Asset>
                <Asset>
                  <Template>Character Audio</Template>
                  <Values>
                    <Sound />
                    <Standard>
                      <GUID>3058061</GUID>
                      <Kommentar>WE3 Intro - Rufus Meldung AUDIO Mission03</Kommentar>
                      <Creator>bombera</Creator>
                      <CreationTime>2011-09-07 21:21</CreationTime>
                      <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                      <LastChangeTime>2012-01-31 10:48</LastChangeTime>
                    </Standard>
                    <Text>
                      <LocaText>
                        <German>
                          <Text>Sie haben sich bewährt! Dafür wartet bereits eine noch größere Herausforderung! Sie sind auf dem direkten Weg an die Spitze.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Sie haben sich bewährt! Dafür wartet bereits eine noch größere Herausforderung! Sie sind auf dem direkten Weg an die Spitze.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                        </German>
                        <English>
                          <Text>You certainly proved yourself! And now an even greater challenge awaits you! You're on the fast track to the top.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>You certainly proved yourself! And now an even greater challenge awaits you! You're on the fast track to the top.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>2</ExportCount>
                        </English>
                        <French>
                          <Text>Vous avez fait vos preuves ! Mais un défi encore plus grand vous attend maintenant ! Vous êtes dans l’ascenseur qui va vous mener au sommet.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </French>
                        <Italian>
                          <Text>Hai sicuramente dimostrato le tue capacità! E adesso ti attende una sfida ancora più grande! Non ci metterai molto ad arrivare in alto.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Hai sicuramente dimostrato le tue capacità! E adesso ti attende una sfida ancora più grande! Non ci metterai molto ad arrivare in alto.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Italian>
                        <Spanish>
                          <Text>¡Sin duda has demostrado tu valía! ¡Y ahora te espera un reto aún mayor! Te diriges a la cima por la vía rápida.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>¡Sin duda has demostrado tu valía! ¡Y ahora te espera un reto aún mayor! Te diriges a la cima por la vía rápida.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Spanish>
                        <Polish>
                          <Text>Udało ci się potwierdzić swą wartość! Teraz czeka cię jeszcze większe wyzwanie! Jesteś w drodze na szczyt.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Udało ci się potwierdzić swą wartość! Teraz czeka cię jeszcze większe wyzwanie! Jesteś w drodze na szczyt.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Polish>
                        <Czech>
                          <Text>Zatím se ukazujete v tom nejlepším světle! A čeká vás další výzva! S takovou budete brzy na vrcholu!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Zatím se ukazujete v tom nejlepším světle! A čeká vás další výzva! S takovou budete brzy na vrcholu!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Czech>
                        <Russian>
                          <Text>Вы показали себя в деле! А теперь вас ждет еще более серьезное испытание! Вы быстро делаете карьеру.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Вы показали себя в деле! А теперь вас ждет еще более серьезное испытание! Вы быстро делаете карьеру.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Russian>
                      </LocaText>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                      <LastGermanText>Und wieder eine größere Herausforderung! Sie sind auf dem direkten Weg an die Spitze.</LastGermanText>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </Asset>
              </Assets>
            </Group>
            <Group>
              <Name>Oilbaron</Name>
              <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
              <Assets>
                <Asset>
                  <Template>CharacterText</Template>
                  <Values>
                    <Sound />
                    <Standard>
                      <GUID>3058029</GUID>
                      <Kommentar>WE3 Intro - Oilbaron</Kommentar>
                      <Creator>petri</Creator>
                      <CreationTime>2011-07-26 14:27</CreationTime>
                      <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                      <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                    </Standard>
                    <Text>
                      <LocaText>
                        <German>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] will mit Ihnen Geschäfte machen.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                        </German>
                        <English>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] wants to do business with you.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </English>
                        <Polish>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] chce robić z tobą interesy.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Polish>
                        <French>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] souhaite faire affaire avec vous.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </French>
                        <Italian>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] vuole fare affari con te.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Italian>
                        <Spanish>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] quiere hacer negocios contigo.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Spanish>
                        <Russian>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] хочет поговорить с вами о деле.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Russian>
                        <Czech>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] s vámi chce obchodovat.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Czech>
                      </LocaText>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330021</SprecherAuswahl>
                      <LastGermanText>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] ist an Handelsbeziehungen interessiert.</LastGermanText>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </Asset>
                <Asset>
                  <Template>Character Audio</Template>
                  <Values>
                    <Sound />
                    <Standard>
                      <GUID>3058030</GUID>
                      <Kommentar>WE3 Intro - Sokov Meldung AUDIO Mission01</Kommentar>
                      <Creator>petri</Creator>
                      <CreationTime>2011-07-26 14:28</CreationTime>
                      <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                      <LastChangeTime>2012-01-31 10:59</LastChangeTime>
                    </Standard>
                    <Text>
                      <LocaText>
                        <German>
                          <Text>Die Finanzkrise ist auch an Sokow Transnational nicht spurlos vorübergezogen. Ich werde alles daran setzen, meine Gewinne wieder zu alter Größe zu bringen.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Die Finanzkrise ist auch an Sokow Transnational nicht spurlos vorübergezogen. Ich werde alles daran setzen, meine Gewinne wieder zu alter Größe zu bringen.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                        </German>
                        <English>
                          <Text>Global Trust's dire financial position has not gone unnoticed by Sokow Transnational. I will do my utmost to maximize my profits again.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Global Trust's dire financial position has not gone unnoticed by Sokow Transnational. I will do my utmost to maximize my profits again.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </English>
                        <French>
                          <Text>La situation financière désastreuse de Global Trust n’a pas échappée à Sokow Transnational. Je ferai tout ce qui est en mon pouvoir pour maximiser mes profits.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </French>
                        <Italian>
                          <Text>Sokow Transnational è a conoscenza della difficile situazione finanziaria della Global Trust. Mi sforzerò di massimizzare nuovamente i miei profitti.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Sokow Transnational è a conoscenza della difficile situazione finanziaria della Global Trust. Mi sforzerò di massimizzare nuovamente i miei profitti.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Italian>
                        <Spanish>
                          <Text>La espantosa situación financiera de Global Trust no le ha pasado inadvertida a Sokow Transnational. Haré todo lo que pueda para volver a maximizar mis beneficios.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>La espantosa situación financiera de Global Trust no le ha pasado inadvertida a Sokow Transnational. Haré todo lo que pueda para volver a maximizar mis beneficios.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Spanish>
                        <Polish>
                          <Text>Zła kondycja finansowa Global Trust nie uszła uwadze Sokow Transnational. Zrobię wszystko, żeby znowu zmaksymalizować zyski.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Zła kondycja finansowa Global Trust nie uszła uwadze Sokow Transnational. Zrobię wszystko, żeby znowu zmaksymalizować zyski.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Polish>
                        <Czech>
                          <Text>Nezáviděníhodná situace Global Trust nám neunikla. Pokusím se znovu maximalizovat svoje zisky.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Nezáviděníhodná situace Global Trust nám neunikla. Pokusím se znovu maximalizovat svoje zisky.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Czech>
                        <Russian>
                          <Text>Затруднительное финансовое положение Глобал Траст не ускользнуло от внимания "Соков Интернационал". Я сделаю все, что смогу, чтобы извлечь из этого максимальную прибыль.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Затруднительное финансовое положение Глобал Траст не ускользнуло от внимания "Соков Интернационал". Я сделаю все, что смогу, чтобы извлечь из этого максимальную прибыль.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Russian>
                      </LocaText>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330021</SprecherAuswahl>
                      <LastGermanText>Die Finanzkrise ist auch an Sokow Transnational nicht spurlos vorübergezogen. Ich werde alles daran setzen, meinen Gewinn wieder zu alter Größe zu bringen.</LastGermanText>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </Asset>
                <Asset>
                  <Template>Character Audio</Template>
                  <Values>
                    <Sound />
                    <Standard>
                      <GUID>3058064</GUID>
                      <Kommentar>WE3 Intro - Sokov Meldung AUDIO Mission02</Kommentar>
                      <Creator>bombera</Creator>
                      <CreationTime>2011-09-07 21:21</CreationTime>
                      <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                      <LastChangeTime>2012-01-31 10:59</LastChangeTime>
                    </Standard>
                    <Text>
                      <LocaText>
                        <German>
                          <Text>Sie haben die Schürfrechte, Sokow Transnational kümmert sich um die Weiterverwertung. Eine Hand wäscht die andere, 'da'?</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Sie haben die Schürfrechte, Sokow Transnational kümmert sich um die Weiterverwertung. Eine Hand wäscht die andere, 'da'?</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                        </German>
                        <English>
                          <Text>You have the mineral rights and Sokow Transnational can take care of the processing. A match made in Heaven, "da"?</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>You have the mineral rights and Sokow Transnational can take care of the processing. A match made in Heaven, "da"?</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>2</ExportCount>
                        </English>
                        <French>
                          <Text>Vous avez les droits miniers et Sokow Transnational peut se charger de l’exploitation. Équitable, "da" ?</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </French>
                        <Italian>
                          <Text>Tu hai le concessioni minerarie e la Sokow Transnational può occuparsi della lavorazione. Praticamente una combinazione perfetta, eh?</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Tu hai le concessioni minerarie e la Sokow Transnational può occuparsi della lavorazione. Praticamente una combinazione perfetta, eh?</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Italian>
                        <Spanish>
                          <Text>Tú tienes los derechos de los minerales y Sokow Transnational puede encargarse de procesarlos. Una pareja perfecta, ¿"da"?</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Tú tienes los derechos de los minerales y Sokow Transnational puede encargarse de procesarlos. Una pareja perfecta, ¿"da"?</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Spanish>
                        <Polish>
                          <Text>Masz prawa do minerałów, a Sokow Transnational może zająć się ich przetwarzaniem. Idealna z nas para, "da"?</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Masz prawa do minerałów, a Sokow Transnational może zająć się ich przetwarzaniem. Idealna z nas para, "da"?</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Polish>
                        <Czech>
                          <Text>Vy máte práva na těžbu a korporace Sokow se postará o zpracování. Je to jako sen, že?</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Vy máte práva na těžbu a korporace Sokow se postará o zpracování. Je to jako sen, že?</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Czech>
                        <Russian>
                          <Text>У вас права на добычу, а Соков Транснационал может организовать сам процесс. Мы просто созданы друг для друга, окей?</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>У вас права на добычу, а Соков Транснационал может организовать сам процесс. Мы просто созданы друг для друга, окей?</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Russian>
                      </LocaText>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330021</SprecherAuswahl>
                      <LastGermanText>Sie haben die Schürfrechte, Sokow kümmert sich um die Weiterverwertung. Eine Hand wäscht die andere, 'da'?</LastGermanText>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </Asset>
                <Asset>
                  <Template>Character Audio</Template>
                  <Values>
                    <Sound />
                    <Standard>
                      <GUID>3058065</GUID>
                      <Kommentar>WE3 Intro - Sokov Meldung AUDIO Mission03</Kommentar>
                      <Creator>bombera</Creator>
                      <CreationTime>2011-09-07 21:21</CreationTime>
                      <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                      <LastChangeTime>2012-02-23 09:58</LastChangeTime>
                    </Standard>
                    <Text>
                      <LocaText>
                        <German>
                          <Text>Mein geschäftlicher Spürsinn sagt mir, dass Sie wieder einige luktrative Geschäfte gebrauchen können. Und in diesen Dingen irre ich mich nie!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Mein geschäftlicher Spürsinn sagt mir, dass Sie wieder einige luktrative Geschäfte gebrauchen können. Und in diesen Dingen irre ich mich nie!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                        </German>
                        <English>
                          <Text>My business instinct tells me that you could use a few more lucrative deals… And I'm never wrong about these things!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>My business instinct tells me that you could use a few more lucrative deals… And I'm never wrong about these things!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>2</ExportCount>
                        </English>
                        <French>
                          <Text>Mon instinct commercial me dit que vous ne seriez pas contre quelques contrats plus lucratifs... Et il ne me trompe jamais !</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </French>
                        <Italian>
                          <Text>Il mio istinto commerciale mi dice che ti servirebbero accordi più redditizi... E su certe cose non mi sbaglio mai!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Il mio istinto commerciale mi dice che ti servirebbero accordi più redditizi... E su certe cose non mi sbaglio mai!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Italian>
                        <Spanish>
                          <Text>Mi instinto para los negocios me dice que te vendrían buen más tratos lucrativos... ¡Y nunca me equivoco con estas cosas!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Mi instinto para los negocios me dice que te vendrían buen más tratos lucrativos... ¡Y nunca me equivoco con estas cosas!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Spanish>
                        <Polish>
                          <Text>Mój instynkt kupiecki mówi mi, że przydałoby ci się parę lukratywnych transakcji... W tych sprawach nigdy się nie mylę!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Mój instynkt kupiecki mówi mi, że przydałoby ci się parę lukratywnych transakcji… W tych sprawach nigdy się nie mylę!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Polish>
                        <Czech>
                          <Text>Můj obchodní instinkt mi říká, že by se vám hodilo pár lukrativních obchodů... A já se nikdy nemýlím!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Můj obchodní instinkt mi říká, že by se vám hodilo pár lukrativních obchodů... A já se nikdy nemýlím!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Czech>
                        <Russian>
                          <Text>Инстинкт бизнесмена подсказывает мне, что вам не помешала бы пара выгодных сделок... В таких вещах я никогда не ошибаюсь!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Инстинкт бизнесмена подсказывает мне, что вам не помешала бы пара выгодных сделок... В таких вещах я никогда не ошибаюсь!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Russian>
                      </LocaText>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330021</SprecherAuswahl>
                      <LastGermanText>Mein geschäftlicher Spürsinn sagt mir, dass Sie wieder einige gute Geschäfte gebrauchen können. Und in diesen Dingen irre ich mich nie!</LastGermanText>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </Asset>
              </Assets>
            </Group>
          </Groups>
        </Group>
        <Group>
          <Name>Outro</Name>
          <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
          <Groups>
            <Group>
              <Name>Rufus</Name>
              <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
              <Assets>
                <Asset>
                  <Template>CharacterText</Template>
                  <Values>
                    <Sound />
                    <Standard>
                      <GUID>3058031</GUID>
                      <Kommentar>Outro WE3</Kommentar>
                      <Creator>petri</Creator>
                      <CreationTime>2011-07-27 10:41</CreationTime>
                      <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                      <LastChangeTime>2012-02-28 17:09</LastChangeTime>
                    </Standard>
                    <Text>
                      <LocaText>
                        <German>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] ist vollends zufrieden mit Ihrer Intervention in dieser Angelegenheit.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                        </German>
                        <English>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] is completely satisfied with your intervention in this matter.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </English>
                        <Polish>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] cieszy się z twojej interwencji w tej sprawie.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Polish>
                        <French>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] approuve totalement votre intervention dans cette affaire.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </French>
                        <Italian>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] esprime la sua completa soddisfazione per i tuoi interventi in questa faccenda.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Italian>
                        <Spanish>
                          <Text>A [THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] le satisface completamente tu participación en este asunto.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Spanish>
                        <Russian>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] всецело доволен тем, как вы разрешили ситуацию.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Russian>
                        <Czech>
                          <Text>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] nemá vůči vaší intervenci v této záležitosti výhrady.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Czech>
                      </LocaText>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                      <LastGermanText>[THIRDPARTY_SENDER_PLAYER] ist vollends Zufrieden mit Ihrer intervention in dieser Angelegenheit.</LastGermanText>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </Asset>
                <Asset>
                  <Template>Character Audio</Template>
                  <Values>
                    <Sound />
                    <Standard>
                      <GUID>3058032</GUID>
                      <Kommentar>WE3 Outro - Rufus Meldung AUDIO Mission01</Kommentar>
                      <Creator>petri</Creator>
                      <CreationTime>2011-07-27 10:48</CreationTime>
                      <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                      <LastChangeTime>2012-01-31 10:48</LastChangeTime>
                    </Standard>
                    <Text>
                      <LocaText>
                        <German>
                          <Text>Sie haben ausgezeichnete Arbeit geleistet. Ich werde dafür sorgen, dass Ihre Leistung angemessen belohnt wird.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Sie haben ausgezeichnete Arbeit geleistet. Ich werde dafür sorgen, dass Ihre Leistung angemessen belohnt wird.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                        </German>
                        <English>
                          <Text>Very good! You have done some outstanding work, something which the firm values very highly.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Very good! You have done some outstanding work, something which the firm values very highly.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </English>
                        <French>
                          <Text>Très bien ! Vous avez accompli un travail remarquable, et la compagnie vous en est très reconnaissante.</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </French>
                        <Italian>
                          <Text>Molto bene! Hai fatto davvero un ottimo lavoro, l'azienda lo apprezza moltissimo.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Molto bene! Hai fatto davvero un ottimo lavoro, l'azienda lo apprezza moltissimo.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Italian>
                        <Spanish>
                          <Text>¡Muy bien! Has hecho un trabajo excelente, algo que la empresa valora mucho.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>¡Muy bien! Has hecho un trabajo excelente, algo que la empresa valora mucho.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Spanish>
                        <Polish>
                          <Text>Bardzo dobrze! Udało ci się wykonać wspaniałą pracę, firma to docenia.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Bardzo dobrze! Udało ci się wykonać wspaniałą pracę, firma to docenia.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Polish>
                        <Czech>
                          <Text>Velmi dobře! Vaší skvělé práce si společnost velice váží.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Velmi dobře! Vaší skvělé práce si společnost velice váží.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Czech>
                        <Russian>
                          <Text>Очень хорошо! Вы проделали выдающуюся работу, а компания очень высоко это ценит.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Очень хорошо! Вы проделали выдающуюся работу, а компания очень высоко это ценит.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Russian>
                      </LocaText>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                      <LastGermanText>Der Aufschwung der Eden Initiative und damit verbundene Faktoren haben ein Loch in die Finanzplanung der Firma gerissen. Die neue Siedlungskampagne sieht zwar Steuererleichterungen vor, aber so bekommen wir die Chance, unsere Verluste durch verstärkten Handel wieder auszugleichen. Und vergessen Sie nicht: Was zählt, ist der Profit!</LastGermanText>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </Asset>
                <Asset>
                  <Template>Character Audio</Template>
                  <Values>
                    <Sound />
                    <Standard>
                      <GUID>3058062</GUID>
                      <Kommentar>WE3 Outro - Rufus Meldung AUDIO Mission02</Kommentar>
                      <Creator>bombera</Creator>
                      <CreationTime>2011-09-07 21:21</CreationTime>
                      <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                      <LastChangeTime>2012-01-31 10:48</LastChangeTime>
                    </Standard>
                    <Text>
                      <LocaText>
                        <German>
                          <Text>Beeindruckende Leistung! Es ist immer wieder eine Freude, mit Profis wie Ihnen zusammenzuarbeiten. Weiter so!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Beeindruckende Leistung! Es ist immer wieder eine Freude, mit Profis wie Ihnen zusammenzuarbeiten. Weiter so!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                        </German>
                        <English>
                          <Text>Impressive performance! It's always a pleasure working with professionals like you. Keep it up!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Impressive performance! It's always a pleasure working with professionals like you. Keep it up!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>2</ExportCount>
                        </English>
                        <French>
                          <Text>Vos performances sont impressionnantes ! C’est toujours un plaisir de travailler avec des professionnels comme vous. Continuez comme ça !</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </French>
                        <Italian>
                          <Text>Una prestazione notevole! È sempre un piacere lavorare con professionisti come te. Continua così!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Una prestazione notevole! È sempre un piacere lavorare con professionisti come te. Continua così!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Italian>
                        <Spanish>
                          <Text>¡Impresionante actuación! Siempre es un placer trabajar con profesionales como tú. ¡Sigue así!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>¡Impresionante actuación! Siempre es un placer trabajar con profesionales como tú. ¡Sigue así!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Spanish>
                        <Polish>
                          <Text>Znakomite osiągnięcie! Praca z takimi zawodowcami jak ty, to zawsze przyjemność. Tak trzymaj!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Znakomite osiągnięcie! Praca z takimi zawodowcami jak ty, to zawsze przyjemność. Tak trzymaj!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Polish>
                        <Czech>
                          <Text>Skvělý výkon! Je dobré vědět, že pracujete s profesionály!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Skvělý výkon! Je dobré vědět, že pracujete s profesionály!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Czech>
                        <Russian>
                          <Text>Я впечатлен! Всегда приятно иметь дело с профессионалами. Продолжайте в том же духе!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Я впечатлен! Всегда приятно иметь дело с профессионалами. Продолжайте в том же духе!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Russian>
                      </LocaText>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                      <LastGermanText>Beeindruckende Leistung! Es ist immer wieder eine Freude, mit Profis wie Ihnen zusammenzuarbeiten.</LastGermanText>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </Asset>
                <Asset>
                  <Template>Character Audio</Template>
                  <Values>
                    <Sound />
                    <Standard>
                      <GUID>3058063</GUID>
                      <Kommentar>WE3 Outro - Rufus Meldung AUDIO Mission03</Kommentar>
                      <Creator>bombera</Creator>
                      <CreationTime>2011-09-07 21:21</CreationTime>
                      <LastChangeUser>seibold</LastChangeUser>
                      <LastChangeTime>2012-01-31 10:48</LastChangeTime>
                    </Standard>
                    <Text>
                      <LocaText>
                        <German>
                          <Text>Sie haben der Firma aus einer schweren Krise geholfen. Sogar der Vorstand ist von Ihren Erfolgen schwer beeindruckt! </Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Sie haben der Firma aus einer schweren Krise geholfen. Sogar der Vorstand ist von Ihren Erfolgen schwer beeindruckt! </LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                        </German>
                        <English>
                          <Text>You helped the company out of a severe crisis; even the Board is impressed by your achievements!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>You helped the company out of a severe crisis; even the Board is impressed by your achievements!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>2</ExportCount>
                        </English>
                        <French>
                          <Text>Vous avez aidé la compagnie à sortir d’une crise grave. Ce que vous avez accompli a beaucoup impressionné le conseil d’administration !</Text>
                          <Status>PreFinal</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </French>
                        <Italian>
                          <Text>Hai aiutato la Compagnia a uscire da una grave crisi. Persino il consiglio d'amministrazione è rimasto colpito dai tuoi risultati!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Hai aiutato la Compagnia a uscire da una grave crisi. Persino il consiglio d'amministrazione è rimasto colpito dai tuoi risultati!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Italian>
                        <Spanish>
                          <Text>Has ayudado a la compañía en una grave crisis, ¡incluso la Junta está impresionada con tus logros!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Has ayudado a la compañía en una grave crisis, ¡incluso la Junta está impresionada con tus logros!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Spanish>
                        <Polish>
                          <Text>Udało ci się zażegnać poważny kryzys - nawet zarząd jest pod wrażeniem twoich dokonań!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Udało ci się zażegnać poważny kryzys - nawet zarząd jest pod wrażeniem twoich dokonań!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Polish>
                        <Czech>
                          <Text>Podařilo se vám pomoci společnosti z krize. Rada vám to nezapomene.</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Podařilo se vám pomoci společnosti z krize. Rada vám to nezapomene.</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Czech>
                        <Russian>
                          <Text>Вы помогли компании пережить суровый кризис - вашими достижениями впечатлен даже Совет Директоров!</Text>
                          <LastFinalText>Вы помогли компании пережить суровый кризис - вашими достижениями впечатлен даже Совет Директоров!</LastFinalText>
                          <Status>Final</Status>
                          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
                        </Russian>
                      </LocaText>
                      <SprecherAuswahl>2330003</SprecherAuswahl>
                      <LastGermanText>Sie haben die Firma aus einer schweren Krise geholfen. Sogar der Vorstand ist von Ihren Erfolgen schwer beeindruckt! </LastGermanText>
                    </Text>
                  </Values>
                </Asset>
              </Assets>
            </Group>
          </Groups>
        </Group>
      </Groups>
    </Group>
    <Group>
      <Name>Technic</Name>
      <UseParentGUIDRange>1</UseParentGUIDRange>
      <Assets>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058010</GUID>
              <Creator>petri</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-21 13:35</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>mais</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2011-11-16 11:52</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>WE3M1_Balancing</Text>
                </German>
                <Czech>
                  <Status>Final</Status>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LokaFlag>0</LokaFlag>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058011</GUID>
              <Creator>petri</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-21 13:35</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>mais</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2011-11-16 11:52</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>WE3M2_Balancing</Text>
                </German>
                <Czech>
                  <Status>Final</Status>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LokaFlag>0</LokaFlag>
              <LastGermanText>WE3M1_Balancing</LastGermanText>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
        <Asset>
          <Template>Standard Text</Template>
          <Values>
            <Standard>
              <GUID>3058012</GUID>
              <Creator>petri</Creator>
              <CreationTime>2011-07-21 13:36</CreationTime>
              <LastChangeUser>mais</LastChangeUser>
              <LastChangeTime>2011-11-16 11:52</LastChangeTime>
            </Standard>
            <SubAssets />
            <TextTemplate />
            <Text>
              <LocaText>
                <German>
                  <Text>WE3M3_Balancing</Text>
                </German>
                <Czech>
                  <Status>Final</Status>
                </Czech>
              </LocaText>
              <LokaFlag>0</LokaFlag>
              <LastGermanText>WE3M1_Balancing</LastGermanText>
            </Text>
          </Values>
        </Asset>
      </Assets>
    </Group>
  </Groups>
</Group>